Hi everyone, welcome to the Domination course.
By the time you've completed this course, you should feel very comfortable and very
confident dominating your clients on cam.
We cover absolutely everything that there is that you need to know about domination.
A couple of the topics that we cover include humiliation, sissification, jerk-off
instruction, financial domination, small penis humiliation, cuckold -
we literally cover everything. We also include a couple of videos and some scripts
and phrases you can say to your clients, stuff that you can use and take with you.
So yeah, we're really excited to have you here and I'm very excited to see your journey
becoming a professional dominatrix. Thank you girlies and see you soon, bye.